Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Administration Records 1853-2002 (bulk, 1929-1995) MS 3009-RG 5
New-York Historical Society
- Series VI. Executive Vice President Kelso Sutton Files, 1968-1994; 53 Linear feet in 53 record cartons
  - Subseries VI.B. Books Group Files, 1983-1993; 22.6 Linear feet in 24 record cartons
    - Video: HBO promotional facilities video tape, circa 1980s (Offsite-box 3808, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (9 min., 15 sec): 3/4 in. On container: "Kelso F. Sutton. HBO promotional facilities video tape. Running time 9:15. Neal Finn 391-0415." On label: "HBO Facilities Promotional tape. 9:15. Neal Finn, Net Ops."
    - Video: How to raise a drug free child, 1989 April 5 (Offsite-box 3808, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (28 min.): 1/2 in. On label: "4/05/89. T-30. 'How to raise a drug free child.' Part 1 of 1. TRT-28:00 (APP)."
    - Video: It happened in Sun Valley, circa 1980s (Offsite-box 3808, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "It happened in Sun Valley." With handwritten note: "Kelso - One of EPL's best speeches ever - at the sales mtg - Enjoy. Jim."
    - Video: Time, Inc. Changes and choices, 1987 September (Offsite-box 3808, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Time Inc. Changes and choices. Version A. September 1987."
    - Video: Time Man of the Year, 1986 December 27 (Offsite-box 3808, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On container: "'TIME Man of the Year. 12/27/86. Produced by Reeves Corporation Services in cooperation with TIME Magazine."
    - Video: The Time of our lives, 1983 October 14 (Offsite-box 3808, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (72 min., 17 sec): 3/4 in. On label: "Date: 10/14/83. Stock # New 60. Title: 'The Time of our lives.' Part # 1 of 2. Running time: 60:00. Audio track # Ch 1 & 2. Overlap: 5:00. Remarks: 1:12:17."
    - Video: Time's Man of the Year, 1985 (Offsite-box 3808, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "TIME's Man of the Year, 1985."
    - Warner New Media, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 10)
    - Warner Publishing Services, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 11)
    - Warner Publishing Services strategic analysis, 1992 August 3 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 12)
  - Subseries VI.C. Board of Directors Executive Officer Files, 1983-1993; 3.6 Linear feet in 5 record cartons
    Contains corporate-level development and strategic planning files, including the work of the Corporate Strategy Group, meeting and conference files, and files about the Time-Warner merger.
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Butterfield Communications Group Strategic overview of the broadcast television industry, 1985 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 13)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Discussion of broadcast television industry, 1985 July 18 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 14)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Discussion of corporate strategy, 1985 March (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 15)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Discussion of the newspaper industry, 1985 July (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 16)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Discussion of the newspaper industry: The newspaper database, 1985 July 15 (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 17)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Discussion of the television production and distribution industry, 1985 September (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 18)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: First Boston Corporation Gulf and Western, 1985 August (Offsite-box 3806, Folder 19)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: First Boston Corporation leveraged employee stock ownership plans (ESOP), 1995 January 18 (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 1)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: First Boston Corporation Knight-Ridder, 1985 (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 2)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: First Boston Corporation "Project Gulf" materials prepared for discussion, 1985 May 31 (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 3)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Infomarketing Group/Butterfield Communications Group prospects for advertising-supported media, 1984 November 15 (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 4)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Management inventory [RESTRICTED], 1985 May 30 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 8)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Memoranda, strategy, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 5)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Memoranda, television programming, 1985 August-September (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 6)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Memoranda, miscellaneous, 1985 March-June (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 7)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Merger and acquisition opportunities, 1985 April 21-May 15 (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 8-10)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Newspaper publishing companies, 1985 (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 11)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: "Tango/Charlie" (CBS), 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 12)
    - Corporate Strategy Group: Ten year financial plan, 1986 July 10 (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 13)
    - Magazine Group: Analyst presentation, 1988 November 9 (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 14)
    - Time Inc. Corporate Strategy Group meeting, Lyford Cay, 1988 May-1989 October (Offsite-box 3809, Folder 15-18)
    - Time Inc. Corporate Strategy Group meeting, Lyford Cay, 1985 October (Offsite-box 3810, Folder 1-2)
    - Time Inc. Corporate Strategy Group meeting, Lyford Cay photograph, circa 1980s (Offsite-box 3810, Folder 3)
    - Time Inc. discussion of corporate strategy, 1988 June (Offsite-box 3810, Folder 4)
    - Time Inc. editorial guidelines manual, 1987 (Offsite-box 3810, Folder 5)
    - Time Inc. publishing public policy issues strategy meeting, 1989 May 1 (Offsite-box 3810, Folder 6)
    - Time-Life Books Steering Committee: McKinsey and Company study group, 1983 January 25-1984 September 19 (Offsite-box 3810, Folder 7-15)
    - Time Warner corporate structure, 1993 (Offsite-box 3811, Folder 1)
    - Time Warner international management directory, 1993 (Offsite-box 3811, Folder 2)
    - Time Warner international management directory (binder cover), 1993 (Offsite-box 3807, Folder 5)
    - Time-Warner merger: Agreement and plan of merger [RESTRICTED], 1989 March 3 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 9)
    - Time-Warner merger: Bank meeting, 1989 June 24 (Offsite-box 3811, Folder 3-4)
    - Time-Warner merger: Board of Directors meeting [RESTRICTED], 1989 March 3 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 10)
    - Time-Warner merger: Board of Directors meeting documents [RESTRICTED], 1989 April 20 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 11)
    - Time-Warner merger: Board of Directors meeting documents [RESTRICTED], 1989 May 16 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 12)
    - Time-Warner merger: Board of Directors meeting materials, 1989 March 3 (Offsite-box 3811, Folder 5)
    - Time-Warner merger: Board of Directors meeting slides, 1989 March 3 (Offsite-box 3811, Folder 6)
    - Time-Warner merger: Board of Directors resolution, 1989 March 3 (Offsite-box 3811, Folder 7)
    - Time-Warner merger: Bridge Loan Facilities, 1989 July 1 (Offsite-box 3811, Folder 8)
    - Time-Warner merger: Information statement and prospectus [RESTRICTED], 1989 September 14 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 13-15)
    - Time-Warner merger: Merger agreement and certificate of designation [RESTRICTED], 1989 November 10 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 16)
    - Time-Warner merger: Paramount Communications v. Time Inc., 1989 July 6-14 (Offsite-box 3811, Folder 9-14)
    - Time-Warner merger: Paramount Communications v. Time Inc. litigation files list, 1989 June 28 (Offsite-box 3811, Folder 15)
  - Subseries VI.D. Executive Vice President Files, 1992-1994; 1.1 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Contains the Full Service Network files, an interactive telecommunications venture by Time Warner, as well as files about multimedia opportunities on the Internet. There are also planning files for the International Silent Auction Society, a subscription club for auctions tested under Sutton.
    - America Online, 1993 (Offsite-box 3812, Folder 1)
    - Bozell Worldwide: "Reality and Blue Sky Realms of Interactive Marketing, Media and Communications", 1993 January (Offsite-box 3812, Folder 2)
    - Electronic superhighway, Montauk Yacht Club, 1993 August 9-10 (Offsite-box 3812, Folder 3)
    - Full Service Network, 1993 (Offsite-box 3812, Folder 4-7)
    - Full Service Network [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 17)
    - Full Service Network advertising, 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 3812, Folder 8)
    - Full Service Network: Time Inc. interviews, 1993 (Offsite-box 3812, Folder 9)
    - Horoscope, 1992 (Offsite-box 3812, Folder 10)
    - International Silent Auction Society, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 3812, Folder 12-16)
    - International Silent Auction Society [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Offsite-box R67, Folder 18)
    - Multimedia and children, 1993 (Offsite-box 3812, Folder 11)
  - Subseries VI.E. Speeches, 1971-1994; 2.7 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
    Contains speeches given by Kelso Sutton at meetings, conferences and other events during his time working for both the Magazine Group and Book Group, as well as speeches by his colleagues. Also contains Sutton's presentations and remarks to the Time Inc. Board of Directors.
    - Board of Directors presentations and/or remarks: Sutton, Kelso, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 3813, Folder 1-4)
    - Executive dialogue, Lyford Cay, Nassau, 1985 (Offsite-box 3813, Folder 5-6)
    - Presentation: Elliman, Donald: Lunch, 1991 (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 9)
    - Speeches: Keylor, Arthur, 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 3813, Folder 7-8)
    - Speeches: Munro, J. Richard: Little, Brown and Company 150th anniversary, 1987 April 30 (Offsite-box 3813, Folder 9)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Miscellaneous, 1971-1984 (Offsite-box 3813, Folder 10-16)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Miscellaneous, 1984 (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 1)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Arthur Thornhill retirement, 1987 May (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 2)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Atlanta Society of Financial Analysts, 1985 March (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 3)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Book-of-the-Month Club, 1987 (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 10)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Books Group European staffers, 1987 May (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 4)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Books Group move, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 11-12)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Books Group vendor conference, 1988 March 29 (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 5)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Corporate circulation strategic planning meeting, Vermont, 1985 September (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 6)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Corporate management, 1992 (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 13-14)
      Includes audiovisual material:
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On container: "Time Inc. Books presentation December 2, 1992."
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "Time Life :60/:30 Trials of Life TOL01-6/3 open ended Time Life NY, NY. 11/24/1992."
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Corporate manufacturing and distribution conference, Lake George, 1985 August (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 7)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Dinner in honor of George Hall, 1992 (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 15)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Full service network / Lee DeBoer meeting, 1993 June (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 16)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Human resources conference, Boca Raton, 1985 April (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 8)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Los Angeles: Automotive dinner and West Coast staff, 1986 (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 17)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Magazine Group staff meetings, 1986 (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 18)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Paper week, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 9)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Postal service meeting, 1986 (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 19)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Progressive Farmer, Callaway Gardens, 1985 April (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 10)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Reginald Brack quarterly meeting, 1993 June (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 20)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Retirement of Rose Epstein, 1990 April (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 21)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Retirement roast of Richard Munro, 1990 May (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 22)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Southern Living sales meeting, Lake Lanier, 1985 April (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 11)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Southern Living sales meeting, 1986 (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 23)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Scott, Foresman and Company national sales conference, 1987 July-1989 January (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 12-14)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Time advertising sales meeting, Arizona, 1985 April (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 15)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Time Distribution Services national sales meeting, 1985 January (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 16)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Time Distribution Services Picture Week meeting, Hilton Head, 1985 August (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 17)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Time Inc. alumni, 1986 (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 24)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Time-Life Books, 1987 December (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 18)
    - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso: Young Presidents' Organization, 1985 October (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 19)
    - Speeches: Miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3814, Folder 20-21)
    - Speeches: Miscellaneous, 1992-1985 (Offsite-box 3815, Folder 1-4)
    - Taiwan remarks, 1993 February (Offsite-box 4272, Folder 25)
    - Tribute to Kelso Sutton slides and script, 1994 (Offsite-box 3815, Folder 5)
- Series VII. Executive Vice President Donald J. Barr TIME Newstour '95 Planning Files, 1994-1996; 1 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  According to his bio file, Donald J. Barr joined Time Inc. in 1957 as part of the Chicago production department. He served in international production, as Time production manager and general manager, then worked at Sports Illustrated (SI) as an associate publisher and advertising sales director. In 1985 he was appointed publisher of SI holding this role for five years before being named executive vice president (EVP) of Time Inc. in October 1990. As EVP, he oversaw Manufacturing and Distribution, Human Resources, Administrative Services, and the Law Department. In 1995, he announced his retirement. His work arranging the 1995 newstour was one of his final projects.
  According to a packet on the history of Time Newstours in Editor-in-Chief Henry Grunwald's files, "the purpose of the Newstour is to give an opportunity to a small group of American leaders to visit areas of the world currently in the news..." The majority of prior newstours were organized by Time Promotion and Public Affairs staff.
  This series contains Barr's records from planning the TIME Newstour '95. Records include information on participants, locations visited, and meetings held, and the logistics of organizing this newstour. Barr's files also contains the Time Public Affairs "master copy of Newstour logistics," a reference guide to organizing a newstour, forwarded to him by Lisa Valk Long.
  The majority of records about Time Newstours are located in the Time Inc. Time Publishing and Business Records (MS 3009-RG 24).
  Organized alphabetically with arrangement imposed. General contains loose material housed by the archivist.
  - Newstour Logistics Handbook, 1995 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 1-3)
  - TIME Newstour '95: General, 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 4-5)
  - TIME Newstour '95: American Trans Air Program Manual, 1995 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 6)
  - TIME Newstour '95: Backgrounder Book, 1995 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 7-8)
  - TIME Newstour '95: Barr's personal Newstour binder, 1995 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 9-12)
  - TIME Newstour '95: Budget binder, 1995 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 13)
  - TIME Newstour '95: Legal information: Cuba and Lebanon licenses, 1995 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 14)
  - TIME Newstour '95: Legal information: Cuba and Lebanon licenses [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Offsite-box R9)
  - TIME Newstour '95: Participants Booklet, 1995 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 15)
  - TIME Newstour '95: Recon Trip Briefing binder, [1995] (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 16)
  - TIME Newstour '95: Schedule and charts, 1995 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 17)
  - TIME Newstour '95: Security issues, 1995 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 18)
  - TIME Newstour '95: Stickers, [1995] (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 19)
  - [TIME Newstour '95?]: Vietnam research, 1994 (Offsite-box 4210, Folder 20)
- Series VIII. Office of the Vice President of Administration and International Files, 1968-1973; 4.34 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
  Charles Bear joined Time Inc. as part of Time-Life International (TLI) in 1945. In 1949, he transferred to Fortune magazine as the business manager. He held positions as the assistant publisher of Fortune and general manager of Architectural Forum before returning to TLI in 1960 as the deputy managing director, then managing director.
  In 1968 TLI dissolved with its functions moving back into Time, Life, and Books. Bear became the vice president of international overseeing all corporate international issues. In 1969 President James Shepley named him to the newly created position of vice president of administration in addition to his existing vice president position. As vice president of administration, Bear also oversaw all divisions not already handled by the existing executive vice presidents including legal, public affairs, personnel, and research and development. Shepley stated Bear was now the pathway for these divisions to communicate with the Office of the President. According to the Department Head Lists, Bear also oversaw Company Services, real estate, and medical. In 1970, the duties of public affairs would shift away from Bear to the new vice president of corporate public affairs. Paul Hale, Charles Terranella and Howard Dunn were assistants to Bear while he was vice president of administration and international.
  In 1971 Bear was named secretary of Time Inc., holding this role through 1972. In 1972, Bear was made a group vice president keeping all his current responsibilities plus overseeing Selling-Areas Marking Inc. (SAMI) and Pioneer Press, subsidiaries of Time Inc. By 1974 he also oversaw Printing Developments, Inc. Bear retired from Time Inc. in 1984.
  Charles Bear files include administrative records from him and his assistants Paul Hale, Charles Terranella and Howard Dunn. There are extensive notes from the assistants to Bear. Some of Dunn's materials state he is J. Winston Fowkles's assistant for Time Life International matters.
  Records include correspondence, memoranda, and notes primarily about personnel and financial policies and issues. The records are a mix of substantive files regarding international and administrative issues for Time Inc. along with other internal office policies such as payroll change procedures or computer upgrades. The correspondence includes correspondence with heads of companies regarding the newstour, discussions of department staff and overhead expenses, and correspondence with foreign publishers affiliated with Time Inc. The "Miscellaneous" folder includes a copy of Time Inc.'s 1973 Standard & Poor's listing form.
  The records include some materials, which may be inherited, from Fowlkes regarding corporate matters and board meetings; and from Manfred Gottfried. Gottfried joined the corporate staff in 1957 with broad assignments from the president including civil defense activities. The records from him encompass mainly administrative areas of accounting and civil defense.
  Organized into three separate runs of alphabetical subject files based on the original order. The three runs are all from the same staff members, have approximately similar date ranges, and do not duplicate folder titles. Because the archivist does not know the reason for the separation and did not find any archival transfer forms explaining the files, they were not integrated into one run of files.
  - Ad sales bonuses, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 1)
  - Advertising: General, 1971 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative action program, 1973 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 3)
  - American Health Corporation, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 4)
  - Auditorium policy, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 5)
  - Cash advance accounts, 1970 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 6)
  - CFIS [Connecticut Foundation for Independent Schools], 1973 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 7)
  - CTI [Computer Television Inc.], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 8)
  - China tour [Newstour], 1972 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 9)
  - Circulation, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 10)
  - Corporate advertising, 1974 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 11)
  - Corporate matters and board meetings [Time-Life International and Corporate International], 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 12)
  - CPR: Fortune project [Center for Political Research: Investment], 1970 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 13-15)
  - Direct mail insurance, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 16)
  - Economic Stabilization Act, 1971 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 17)
  - Editions Robert Laffont, 1967-1970 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 18)
  - Equity advertising, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 19)
  - Equity method accounting, 1971 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 20)
  - Evaluation procedures [for staff], 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 21)
  - Exhibit Hall and Reception Center, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 22-23)
  - Guild [Newspaper Guild of New York], 1973 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 24)
  - Internal magazine distribution (special projects), 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 25)
  - Legal, 1973 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 26)
  - Life syndication, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 27-28)
  - List fatigue, 1972 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 29)
  - Microfiche, 1970 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 30)
  - Minority businesses, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 600, Folder 31)
  - Minority Business Directory of the Greater New York Area, 1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 2)
  - NFTC [National Foreign Trade Council] and AMA material, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper operating division, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 4)
  - "NO" letters for acquisitions, 1973 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 5)
  - Outside subscriptions, 1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 6)
  - Payroll change procedure, 1969 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 7)
  - Periodicals: Time Inc. subscriptions, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 8)
  - Personnel department, 1973 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 9)
  - Personnel: ID cards, 1970 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 10)
  - Personnel: Insurance, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 11)
  - Personnel: Management, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 12)
  - Personnel: Management [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Offsite-box R16)
  - Personnel: Minority groups, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 13-14)
  - Personnel: Minority groups [RESTRICTED], 1969-1971 (Offsite-box R16)
  - Personnel: Moratorium, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 15)
  - Personnel: Payroll change authorization, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 16)
  - Personnel: Payroll removal [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Offsite-box R16)
  - Personnel: Trainee program, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 17)
  - Postage, 1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 18)
  - Preferred stock, 1970 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 19)
  - President's report (Divisional memoranda and status reports), 1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 20)
  - Proposal for Publication: to people who move, 1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 21)
  - 34th Floor reception desk, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 22)
  - Requisitions, 1970 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 23)
  - Retainers, 1963-1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 24-25)
  - SAMI [Selling-Areas Marketing Inc.], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 26)
  - Satellite, 1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 27)
  - SEAMEO ads, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 28)
  - Special functions, 1973 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 29)
  - Staff additions/replacement, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 30)
  - Staff reduction: US, 1970 (Offsite-box 601, Folder 31)
  - Staff reduction: US [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Offsite-box R16)